- id: ckw-l04-1480
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ネット
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1483
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ガス
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1492
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - パン
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1537
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ライン
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1540
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - コース
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1560
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - タバコ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1567
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - カメラ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1574
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - テーマ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1585
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - テーブル
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1587
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ベッド
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1598
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - プロ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1607
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - トップ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1618
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - イン
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1625
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ボタン
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l04-1629
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - コンピューター
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  invulnerable: false
  max_stage: -1
  learned: false
  hidden: false
  befuddlers: []
